Daniel Kalumba Tshikomba

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPPER

ohdearteddy@icloud.com 🔀

+90 548 871 26 16

Nicosia, CY 💡

teddy-webdev.github.io 🌐

SUMMARY

I am a junior web developer with three years of experience. I have a strong background in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I am also proficient in PHP, MySQL, and Apache. I am a quick learner and have a strong work ethic. I am looking for a position that will challenge me and help me grow as a developer.

SKILLS

HTML		MySQL	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$
CSS	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$	Bootstrap 5	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
JavaScript	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$	Python	$\bullet \bullet \circ \circ \circ$
React JS		Node JS	• • • • •
PHP	• • • • •		

EXPERIENCE

Junior Web Developer

Alemdar Teknik, LTD. Jan 2022 - Present

Developed and managed a responsive website to drive sales for the company.

Setup database integrated WordPress/HTML/CSS/JS/MySQL into the CMS and conducted day-to-day maintenance of the websites, resulting in a 25.8% increase in turnover.

Collaborated with marketing and project management teams to deliver projects ontime and with the highest standard, increasing over 12% of clients numbers over a 1year period.

Junior Web Developer - Intern

Alemnet Network May 2021 - Jan 2022

- Helped Senior Web Developer to maintain websites
- Learned a Javascript framework (React).
- Practiced more on my coding skills

PROJECTS

Website Portfolio

Main Developer Sep 2022 - Present

My personal website was designed and developed by myself and is currently being maintained. Deployed on Github.

Quotes generator Web App

main developer Aug 2022 - Aug 2022

Currency Exchange platform

Main Developer Sep 2022 - Sep 2022

Worked on this project using Javascript, HTML and CSS, fetching data from a currency exchange api.

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

Near East University Sep 2020 - Present

Learning Web and Software Development at Near East University

High School Diploma

Junior Seminary of Mugeri 2013 - 2018

LANGUAGES

English French

••••

Korean Turkish

